in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can use inkscape to create this
如何使用Inkscape来创建
Elegant Style logo design and if you
优雅风格的标志设计，如果你
want to follow along with what I'm doing
想跟随我正在做的事情吗？
in this lesson I will have a link in the
在这一课中，我将在
description of the video to where you
视频的描述，您可以在其中
can download the fonts that I used here
我可以下载我在这里使用的字体
and I'll also include a download link to
我还将包括一个下载链接，以
the file itself in case you want to skip
文件本身，以防您想要跳过
the tutorial and just use this design so
教程，只需使用此设计即可
I'll come over here into a new document
我会到这里来取一份新的文件
and we will get started the first thing
我们第一件事就是开始
I'm going to do is grab my pen tool
我要做的就是拿起我的钢笔工具
which is located over here in the
它位于这里的
toolbar or you can access it by pressing
工具栏，或者您可以通过按
the letter B on your keyboard I'm going
你键盘上的字母B我要走了
to come up here to the settings and I'm
来到这里的布景，我是
going to make sure I have the spiral
我要确保我有螺旋线
path option enabled and then I'm going
路径选项已启用，然后我要
to hold the control key and click once
按住Ctrl键并单击一次
on the canvas to draw a line and bring
在画布上画一条线，并带来
this line straight up and while still
这条线笔直向上，同时保持静止
holding control click again and then we
按住Ctrl键再次点击，然后我们
can let go of control and bring the line
可以放开控制，把线带到
out here and then click again and now I
在这里，然后再次点击，现在我
can continue drawing this curve until it
可以继续绘制这条曲线，直到它
spirals to the inside like that once
像这样向内盘旋一次
you're happy with the placement you can
你对你能找到的位置很满意
press the enter key to place it and if
按Enter键将其放置，如果
you're not entirely happy with how it
你并不完全满意它的方式
looks you can come over here to the edit
看来你可以到这里来编辑了
paths by nodes edit paths by nodes tool
按节点编辑路径工具按节点编辑路径
and zoom in on this and just adjust
把这个放大，然后调整
these nodes a little bit now since this
这些节点现在有一点了，因为这
is a Spyro path it will be a little hard
是一条斯皮罗之路，这会有点难
to control but that's to ensure that it
控制，但这是为了确保它
remains fluid and smooth so I'm going to
保持流畅和光滑，所以我要
adjust this a little bit until I'm happy
稍微调整一下，直到我满意为止
with how it looks and I think that looks
它看起来是什么样子，我觉得它看起来
pretty good right there what I'm looking
就在那里很好，就是我正在看的
for mainly is I want to make sure
主要是我想确保
there's an equal amount of space going
有同样大小的空间
through here I don't want too much space
通过这里，我不想要太多的空间
on one side I want it to look fairly
一方面，我想让它看起来公平
even so now that that's said I'm going
即便如此，既然说了，我还是要去
to zoom out
缩小的步骤
I'm going to take this node right here
我要把这个节点放在这里
click on it to select it let me Zoom
点击它将其选中，让我缩放
down a little bit I'm going to select
再往下一点，我要选择
this node right here and then I'm going
这个节点就在这里，然后我要
to hold the control key and just click
按住Ctrl键并单击
and drag that node up like that I want
然后像我想要的那样向上拖动那个节点
to shorten that a little bit because now
简而言之，因为现在
I'm going to grab the selection tool and
我要拿起选择工具
I'm going to right click this and go to
我要右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate and I'm going to flip it
复制品，我要把它翻过来
vertically and horizontally and I'm
垂直和水平，我是
going to bring this down here on this
我要把这个带到这里来
side now to snap these together I'm
现在站在一边，把这些放在一起，我
going to come up here and click on this
我要在这里点击这个
magnet icon to enable snapping and I
启用捕捉和I的磁铁图标
just want to make sure I have these
我只想确保我有这些
simple controls in place I want these
简单的控制措施到位，我想要这些
two options highlighted and now I can
突出显示了两个选项，现在我可以
zoom in on this and snap this onto the
放大此图并将其捕捉到
line I'm bring that up a little bit I'm
我会稍微提一下这个问题我是
just eyeballing this here and that looks
只是看看这个，那个看起来
pretty good as it is now I'm going to
像现在这样很好，我要
create another one for this side so let
为这一侧再创建一个，这样就让
me right click this and go to duplicate
我右键单击此选项，然后转到复制
again and I'm going to take this one I'm
再来一次，我要选这个我要
going to flip it vertically and I'm
我要垂直翻转它，然后我
going to hold my control key and scale
按住我的控制键和刻度键
this one down a little bit now before I
现在这个稍微往下一点，然后我
do that let me undo what I just did
这样做，让我撤销我刚才所做的
right there before you scale that down
就在那里，在你缩小规模之前
make sure you have this setting disabled
确保您已禁用此设置
this option here that says when scaling
此处的选项表示在扩展时
objects scale the stroke width by the
对象将笔划宽度缩放为
same proportion we want that turned off
与我们希望关闭的比例相同
for this tutorial so make sure that's
对于本教程，请确保
disabled and then scale this down so
禁用，然后将其缩小，以便
that it maintains the same stroke width
它保持相同的笔划宽度
and I'm going to I'm going to place this
我要我要把这个放在
one I'm going to snap it right over here
一，我要在这里把它拍下来
right about there I may make this one a
就在那里，我可能会把这件事做成
little bigger I don't like how small
再大一点，我不喜欢这么小
that one is I'll make that a little
那个是，我会把它弄得有点
bigger and I'll bring that down
更大的，我会把它降下来的
here so now that that's in place let me
在这里，既然已经就位，让我
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
and I'm going to go back to my pen tool
我要回去拿我的钢笔工具了
cool and I'm going to draw another
太棒了，我要再画一幅
little line coming off of the center of
从中央出来的一条小线
this line here so let me snap to the
这条线在这里，所以让我抓住
line hold control bring the line
按住线路控制使线路接通
Straight Up Click again and then bring
向上直击再次点击，然后带上
this one out here right about there
这个就在这里，就在那里
press enter and there you go that's
按Enter键，然后就可以了
about what I'm looking for and again if
关于我正在寻找的东西，如果
you're not happy with the placement you
你对你的安置不满意
could just grab the nodes tool and
只需抓取节点工具并
adjust it until it looks good I'm going
调整它，直到它看起来很好，我要走了
to take this and bring this down a
把这个拿下来，把它降下来
little bit I'm going to hold control
我要掌握一点控制权
while I do this so that it snaps or so
当我这样做的时候，它就会断掉
that it locks it onto the vertical axis
它把它锁在垂直轴上
and let me right click this and
让我用鼠标右键点击它
duplicate it and I'm going to flip this
复制它，我要把它翻过来
vertically and horizontally and bring
垂直和水平，并带来
this down here so that we have another
在这下面，所以我们有另一个
piece down here going the opposite way
从这里下来，往相反的方向走
and that right there is what we're
而这就是我们正在做的
looking for so what I'll do next is I'm
寻找所以我下一步要做的是
going to draw another line coming out of
我要画出另一条线
the top right here I'm going to grab my
上衣就在这里，我要拿起我的
pen tool again I'm going to snap to this
又是钢笔工具，我要抓住这个
intersecting area and then just click
相交区域，然后单击
and drag or just click a couple of times
然后拖动或只点击几次
rather to draw a line sort of like that
而是像这样划一条线
and press enter it's not going to look
然后按Enter键它不会看起来
good at first but that's okay CU we're
起初很好，但没关系，CU，我们
going to go to the edit pads by no noes
我绝对不会去编辑键盘的
tool and adjust this until it looks
工具并调整它，直到它看起来
right so I'm going to move this you got
好的，我要把你拿到的这个
to be careful of the snapping here there
要当心这里和那里的抓拍
we go and maybe I'll adjust that a
我们一起去，也许我会把它调整成
little
一点儿
bit okay that looks good as it is okay
有点好，看起来还不错。
so let me zoom out now what I'm going to
现在让我把我要做的事情放大一下
do is I'm going to grab my selection
我要做的就是去拿我的选择
tool I want to select all of these
工具我想选择所有这些
pieces and I want to convert them from
我想把它们从
spiral paths to just regular paths so
螺旋路径到规则路径，因此
I'll come up here to path and I will
我会走到这里来，我会
select object to path
选择要进行路径的对象
and now I'm going to group them together
现在我要把它们组合在一起
by going to object group and now I'm
通过转到对象组，现在我
going to click on it to get the rotation
我要点击它来获得轮换
handles and I want to rotate this around
把手，我想把这个旋转一下
clockwise until it's sitting flat like
顺时针方向，直到它像这样平坐
this and what I'm looking for is the
这就是我要找的
bottom of this side and the bottom of
这一侧的底部和
this side I want to make sure they're
在这一边，我想确保他们
both sitting flat on the bounding box of
两个人都平坐在
the selection while I rotate it so let
当我旋转选区时，让它
me just make sure um let me just make
我只是确保，嗯，让我只做
sure everything's even that looks pretty
当然，一切都很平坦，看起来很漂亮
good as it is and now I can zoom out and
尽管它很好，现在我可以缩小和
now we're going to ungroup this so let's
现在我们要把它解开，所以让我们
come up here to object and go to
到这里来反对，然后去
ungroup and then open up the fill and
取消分组，然后打开填充并
stroke menu and I'll do that just by
笔划菜单，我将只通过
double clicking this black stripe down
向下双击这条黑色条纹
here and that'll open up the fill and
这里和那里会打开填充物和
stroke menu I want to come over here to
我想来这里看看中风菜单
the stroke style Tab and I want to
笔划样式选项卡和我想要
increase the width so I'm going to click
增加宽度，这样我就可以点击
on this plus icon and hold that click to
在这个加号图标上，并按住那个点击
make this to make those lines thicker
做这个可以让这些线条更粗
and I want to give them rounded
我想给他们四舍五入
caps and now I'm going to click off of
帽子，现在我要点击
it to deselect everything I'm going to
我要取消选择我要做的一切
add little circles at the ends of these
在这些东西的末端加一些小圆圈
uh lines here show you what I mean in
呃，这里的线条显示了我的意思
this design over here I have these
这个设计在这里，我有这些
little circles on these ends so let me
这些末端的小圆圈，所以让我
show you how you can do that I'm going
让你看看你能做什么我要去
to select this object right here first
要首先在此处选择此对象
and I'll come over here to the markers
我会走到这里的标记前
in the stroke style tab I'm going to
在笔划样式选项卡中，我将执行以下操作
come over here to where it says markers
过来，到上面写着记号的地方
and I want to add an ends marker I'm
我想添加一个结束标记，我是
going to click on this drop down and I'm
点击这个下拉列表，我就会
going to choose this round option but
我要选择这一轮的选项，但是
when you do that it's going to be a
当你做到这一点时，这将是一个
little too big so I'm going to bring
有点太大了，所以我要带上
that down in size a little bit I'm going
尺寸稍微小一点，我要去
to manually type in the default size is
手动键入默认大小是
one I'm going to bring this down to
我将把这一点归结为
about 0.5 and see how that
大约0.5，看看这是如何
looks okay that's a a good proportion
看起来不错，这是一个很好的比例
right there so I'll leave that as it is
就在那里，所以我就让它保持原样
and I'm going to do the same thing over
我会重新做同样的事情
here I'm going to apply that to this
在这里，我将把它应用到这个
object as well I'm going to apply that
对象，我将应用它
same marker now now that you applied the
现在相同的标记，因为您将
first marker you should have it up here
第一个记号笔你应该把它放在这里
in your recently used markers and you
在你最近用过的记号笔和你
can just select it and you won't have to
只需选择它，您就不必
resize this one it'll inherit the size
调整这个的大小它将继承这个大小
of the previous
上一次
one and I'll apply that to this part as
一，我将把它应用于这一部分
well let me come up here and choose uh
好的，让我到这里来，选择，嗯
the same
一样的
marker and now I'm just going to put
记号笔，现在我要把
just as like a decorative element I'm
就像一个装饰性的元素，我
going to put three little circles in
我要把三个小圆圈放进去
there so let me come back in here and
所以让我回到这里，然后
add those three little circles let me
加上那三个小圆圈让我
grab my circles and ellipses tool I'm
抓起我的圆圈和省略号工具
going to turn off snapping right now
我现在要关闭捕捉
that's just going to get in the way and
这只会阻碍我们的发展
I'll hold control and click and drag to
我将按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动
draw perfectly around Circle go back to
完美地绕着圆绘制返回到
my selection
我的选择
tool and I will make this a little
Tool和我会让这件事变得有点
bigger actually no I'll leave that as it
更大的，实际上不，我就不说了。
is I'll right click it go to duplicate
我会用鼠标右键点击它去复制
and I'll make this one a little
我会把这个做得有点
bigger and then I'll create one more
更大的，然后我会再创造一个
right click duplicate and I'll make this
右键单击复制，我将使其成为
one even even
甚至一个偶数
bigger holding control while I do this
当我这样做的时候更大的控制力
to lock the aspect ratio there we go now
为了锁定纵横比，我们现在开始
I'm going to zoom
我要变焦了
out okay that looks pretty good so what
好的，看起来很不错，那又怎么样？
I'm going to do now is I'm going to
我现在要做的是我要
select all of this well first of all let
把这一切都选好首先让
me click on one of these and find out
我点击其中一个，就会发现
what exactly the stroke weight is so for
笔划粗细到底是为了什么
mine the stroke weight is six so
我的划水重量是六码。
whatever your number is keep that in
不管你的号码是多少，把它留在里面
mind we're going to use that in just a
请注意，我们将在一个
minute let me select all of this go to
分钟让我选择所有这些转到
object group and now I'm going to create
对象组，现在我要创建
a Circle so I'm going to grab my circles
一个圆圈，所以我要抓住我的圆圈
and ellipses tool click and drag while
和省略号工具单击并拖动时
holding control to create a perfectly
保持控制，创建一个完美的
round circle and I want to give this the
圆的圆圈，我想给这个
same properties that this these objects
与这些对象相同的属性
have so I'm going to remove the fill by
所以我要移除填充物
clicking the Red X and I'm going to hold
点击红色X，我将按住
shift and click on the color black to
按住Shift键并单击黑色以
apply a stroke and it looks like it
应用笔划，看起来就像是
inherited that stroke width already so I
已经继承了该笔划宽度，所以我
don't have to manually type that in if
如果出现以下情况，则不必手动键入
this were any other number than six I'd
这个数字不是6，我想
have to type that in and press enter but
我必须输入并按Enter键，但是
it looks like I'm good to go so let me
看起来我可以走了，所以让我走吧
take this and move this over I'm going
拿着这个，把这个挪过去，我要走了
to scale this down accordingly I'll
为了相应地缩小规模，我将
bring it down maybe that much
把它降下来，也许有那么多
and I want to make sure that this is
我想要确保这是
sitting on the same horizontal plane
坐在同一水平面上
that this object is so let me select
这个物体是如此的让我选择
this object hold shift select this
此对象按住Shift键选择此选项
object and then open up the aligned
对象，然后打开对齐的
distribute menu by going to object and
通过转到对象和分发菜单分发菜单
aligned
对齐
distribute and I'm going to choose last
分发，我将选择最后一个
selected from the relative two dropdown
从相对两个下拉列表中选择
and I want to choose this option down
我想从下面这个选项中选择
here that says align bottom edges and
这里说的是对齐底部边缘和
that's going to put both of those on the
这将把这两个人都放在
same horizontal plane and I'm going
同样的水平面，我要去
click off of that to deselect it and
单击该选项以取消选择它，然后
then I'll take this one and just move
那我就买这一辆，然后搬走。
this in a little bit and I'm holding
在这一点上，我拿着
control while I click and drag so that I
控件，同时单击并拖动，以便我
lock it onto that horizontal plane and I
把它锁在那个水平面上，然后我
don't lose that alignment that I just
别失去我刚才说的那条线
made okay so let me take this object now
做好了，所以现在让我拿着这个物体
right click it go to duplicate I'm going
右键单击Go以复制I‘m go
to flip this one
来翻转这一张
horizontally hold control and move this
水平按住Ctrl键并移动此
one over here just like
一个在这里，就像
that and now I'm going to select both of
现在我要选择这两个选项
these I'm holding shift while I click on
这些我在按住Shift键的同时单击
each of them to select them both and I
他们中的每一个都要选择他们和我
want to group them together we'll go to
想把它们组合在一起，我们会去
object group and I want to Center it on
对象组和我想要将其居中
this circle just to make sure that
这个圆圈只是为了确保
everything is perfectly symmetrical I'll
一切都是完全对称的，我会
select the uh Center on vertical axis
选择呃垂直轴上的中心
there we go and now I can ungroup
我们走了，现在我可以解开了
everything so I'll go to object and
所有的一切，所以我会去反对
select
选择
ungroup and now I'm going to put another
解组，现在我要把另一个
Circle in the center here so let me take
在这里的中心圈，所以让我拿
this circle right click it go to
这个圆圈右键单击它，转到
duplicate hold control and shift and
重复按住Ctrl和Shift并
scale this down about that much and in
缩小到差不多大小，然后在
here you can put whatever you want
你可以在这里放任何你想放的东西
whether it be a letter or an icon or any
无论是字母、图标还是任何
other graphical depiction for my
我的其他图形描述
demonstration I use the inkscape logo I
演示我使用Inkscape徽标I
figured it makes sense since this is an
我想这是有道理的，因为这是一个
inkscape tutorial but you could put
Inkscape教程，但您可以将
whatever you want in there I'm just
不管你在里面想要什么，我只是
going to leave it blank for now and now
暂时将其留空
I'm going to put some lines underneath
我要在下面画几条线
it here if you notice I had some lines
如果你注意到我有一些台词的话
going underneath these
在这些下面
elements so let me come back in here I'm
元素，让我回到这里，我是
going to grab my pen tool again let me
再去拿我的钢笔工具让我
choose the regular pen mode and then
选择常规笔模式，然后
I'll come out here click to add a point
我会在这里点击添加一点
hold control bring the line straight
按住Ctrl键，把线拉直
across right towards the end of the
在接近尾声的时候穿过
other side click again and now we can
另一边再次点击，现在我们可以
let go of control and and press enter to
松开Ctrl和，然后按Enter键
have that line made and I want to make
把这句台词做好了，我想做
that stroke the same size let me grab my
同样大小的笔划让我抓起我的
selection tool I'll come back over here
选择工具，我会回到这里
to the fill in stroke menu the stroke
到填充笔划菜单中的笔划
style tab I'll change this to
样式选项卡我要将其更改为
six I want this to have rounded caps and
六个我想要这个有圆形的盖子和
I'm going to put those markers on the
我要把那些记号笔放在
ends of these so let me use this drop
这些的末端，让我用这一滴
down and select those markers for the
向下并选择这些标记
first and the last the start and the end
第一次和最后一次开始和结束
point of that path and it now has those
这条路的终点，它现在有
markers so let me make another copy of
所以让我再复制一份
this now I'm going to right click it and
现在我要用鼠标右键点击它
go to duplicate hold control and bring
转到复制保留控件并带上
this one down here about that much now
这个就在这里，差不多了
the amount of spacing between these two
这两者之间的间隔量
lines I'm going to use these circles as
线条我将用这些圆圈作为
a reference I want the spacing between
我想要一个引用之间的间距
these two lines to be about equal to the
这两条线大约等于
spacing between these two circles so I'm
这两个圆圈之间的间距，所以我
just going to eyeball that and use my
只是去看看，然后用我的
own judgment it just gives the design an
自己的判断它只是给了设计一个
overall more balanced and symmetrical
整体上更加平衡和对称
look and once that's in place I'm going
听着，一旦放好了，我就走了
to hold control and shift and I'm just
保持控制和换挡，而我只是
going to scale this down a little bit I
我要把这件事缩小一点
want this line to be a little shorter
我想把这条线缩短一点
than the other line and that right there
而不是另一条线和那边的那条线
is what we're going for so now we're
就是我们要做的，所以现在我们
going to add our text
我要添加我们的文本
let me grab the text tool click and for
让我抓起文本工具，点击并获取
this demonstration I'm just going to
这个演示我要做的是
write
写
elegant grab my selection tool and I'm
优雅地拿起我的选择工具，我就
going to open up the text editor which
要打开文本编辑器，其中
can be accessed by uh going to you can
可以通过呃转到您可以访问
use this icon down here in the bottom
使用下面底部的这个图标
right of the screen this letter T click
点击屏幕右侧的此字母T
on that and now we have our text editor
现在我们有了我们的文本编辑器
so let me find the font that I'm using
所以让我找到我正在使用的字体
it's called
它被称为
Brittanic there we go I'll click apply
不列颠语，我们开始，我将点击应用
and I'm just going to scale this up to
我只想把这件事扩大到
make make it an appropriate size for the
使其成为适用于
logo maybe I'll scale this down a little
LOGO，也许我会把它缩小一点
bit and again we're always holding
一次又一次，我们总是握着
control when we scale so that it locks
控制何时缩放以使其锁定
the aspect ratio if you let go of
放手时的纵横比
control you get a lot of distortion
控制会产生很大的失真
which you don't want and now I'm just
这是你不想要的，现在我只是
going to write logo in a different font
将用不同的字体书写徽标
next to it so let me go back over here
在它旁边，所以让我回到这里
to my text tool click again and I'm just
到我的文本工具，再次点击，我只是
going to use all caps
将使用全部大写字母
logo and the font for this one is
徽标，这个标志的字体是
monserat monserat medium and again I'll
Monserat Monserat一次又一次地
have the links to these fonts where you
有指向这些字体的链接，您可以在其中
can download them and install them in
可以将它们下载并安装在
the descript description of the video
视频的描述性描述
These are free fonts so you should be
这些都是免费字体，所以你应该
able to use them without a problem let
能够毫无问题地使用它们
me move this in
我把这个搬进来
here scale it up so it's about the same
在这里，将其放大，使其大致相同
size and I want to decrease the the
我想把尺码改小一点
spacing between these letters so let me
这些字母之间的间隔，所以让我
come back in here to my text tool I'm
回到我的文本工具里来，我是
going to place the cursor between these
将光标放在这两个之间
two letters and I'm going to hold my ALT
两个字母，我要保持我的ALT
key or if you're on Mac it would be the
键，或者如果您使用的是Mac，它将是
option key and then use the left Arrow
Option键，然后使用向左箭头
just to bring that
只是为了把它带来
in and I'll do the same thing over here
我会在这里做同样的事情
I'll move the cursor over here holding
我会将光标移动到这里，按住
my option key or ALT key and just use
我的Option键或Alt键，只需使用
using the arrows to bring those letters
用箭头把那些字母
closer
更近一些
together now I'm going to grab my
现在我要一起去拿我的
selection tool select both of these and
选择工具同时选择这两项和
I'm just going to scale this up so that
我只想把它放大，这样
it fits the logo more
它更适合这个标志
nicely and at this point the problem we
很好，在这一点上，我们的问题是
have now is that the design doesn't look
现在有的是设计看起来不像
very consistent the lines of the
非常一致的线条
ornaments here are much thinner than the
这里的装饰品比
lines of the letters uh an easy little
一行行字母，呃，一个简单的小
trick to fix that you could just select
修复此问题的技巧，您只需选择
everything hold your control key and
一切都按住你的控制键
scale it down a little bit
把它缩小一点
and as you scale It Down The Strokes
当你按比例缩小时，笔划
will remain the same weight but they
将保持相同的重量，但它们
will just look bigger because they're
只会看起来更大，因为他们
being sized smaller and I'll just bring
尺码变小了，我就带上
this down until it looks pretty
把这个放下来，直到它看起来漂亮
consistent with the weight of the
与重物的重量一致
letters and that's really the secret
字母，这才是真正的秘密
here to making this design look good you
为了让这个设计看起来更好
want all of the lines to be a consistent
希望所有的行都是一致的
weight so that it has a uniform
重量，这样它就有一个统一的
look okay that looks good as it is let
看，好的，看起来还不错。
me uh let me update the spacing now a
我，呃，让我更新一下间隔，现在是
little bit I'm going to move this down
我要把这个往下移一点
I'm going to move this line let me
我要移动这条线，让我
deselect that
取消选择该选项
I'm going to move this line down a
我要把这条线往下移一步
little bit and now I'm going to adjust
一点点，现在我要调整一下
the spacing in here to accommodate the
这里的间距用来容纳
spacing change that I made there let me
我在那里所做的间距更改让我
scale that down a little bit I'm holding
把它缩小一点，我拿着
control and shift while I scale this
在我缩放时按住Ctrl键和Shift键
inward so that I don't lose the
向内，这样我就不会失去
orientation with the circle above
使用上面的圆圈确定方向
it and there we go that should do it for
它和我们去那里，应该做的事情
this tutorial that is how you can create
本教程就是您如何创建
these decorative elements to make an
这些装饰元素可以使
elegant style logo using inkscape if you
使用Inkscape的优雅风格徽标，如果您
found this lesson useful then consider
觉得这一课很有用，然后考虑
check checking out my inkscape master
签出我的Inkscape母版
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
在你想要的任何时候从我这里，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
你不需要缴纳月费
just pay $17 one time and you're in for
只需一次性支付17美元，你就会面临
Life I'll have some information about
我会有一些关于生活的信息
that down below if you want to check
如果你想检查的话，请在下面
that out as always thanks for
一如既往地感谢
watching
看
[Music]
[音乐]
oh
哦